Finding Aid for the Randall Stewart Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Randall Stewart Paper
Undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0420
1.26 linear feet
Randall Stewart: A Chronology
1896. Born in Fayetteville, Tennessee, July 25.
1898. His family moved to Nashville where he grew up and was educated.
1917. Was graduated from Vanderbilt University as Founder’s Medalist.
1917-1920. Instructor of English at the University of Oklahoma.
1918. Served briefly in the armed forces.
1920. Married Cleone Odell in Oklahoma City.
1921. Awarded master of arts degree by Harvard University.
1921-1922. Instructor, U. S. Naval Academy.
1922-1925. Assistant Professor, University of Idaho.
1927-1931. Instructor, Yale University.
1930. Awarded doctor of philosophy degree by Yale.
1931-1934. Assistant Professor, Yale.
1932-1939. Associate Editor, New England Quarterly.
1934-1937. Professor, Vanderbilt.
1937-1955. Professor, Brown University.
1943. Guggenheim Fellow.
1947-1948. Visiting Professor, Yale University.
1949-1950. Chairman, Department of English, Brown.
1949-1950. Visiting Professor, Connecticut College.
1951. Chairman, American Literature Group, Modern Language Association.
1955-1963. Professor of English and Chairman, Department of English, Vanderbilt University.
1956. Fugitive Reunion.
1958. Mrs. Harold S. Vanderbilt Literary Symposium established.
1963-1964. Professor, Vanderbilt.
1964. Died June 17.
- RANDALL STEWART COLLECTION
  - Correspondence-Outgoing. Letters are chronologically arranged. Nov. 23, 1955 to Oct. 1, 1959. Undated placed at end. See Index to Outgoing Correspondence. (Box 1, Folder 1-18)
  - Correspondence-Incoming. Chronologically arranged. March 2, 1932 - Dec. 4, 1967. Undated. See Index to Incoming Correspondence. (Box 1, Folder 19-48)
  - Fugitive Reunion Arrangements - Miscellaneous. (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Calendars of Events and Guest List, Fugitive Reunion. (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Fugitive Finances. Vouchers, financial statements regarding the handling of finances for the Fugitive Reunion. (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Fugitive Conference Dinner Programs enclosed in Harvie Branscomb letter, May 8, 1956. (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Fugitive Conference Clippings, Jan 2.0 to June, 1956. Undated. (Box 2, Folder 53-55)
  - Fugitive Reunion Photos Taken by Merrill Moore. (Box 2, Folder 56-57)
  - Book Reviews - Pertaining to R. C. Beatty’s column. (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Stewart’s Class Roll Books, For years 1947, 1955, 1956, 1958. (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Articles about Stewart - Two. (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Pamphlets. (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - One photograph of Donald Davidson effigy. (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Miscellaneous - mainly mailing lists. (Box 2, Folder 63)
- SUPPLEMENTARY DESCRIPTION
  - The following describes Randall Stewart’s papers as they were arranged by topic in Dr. Stewart’s files. Letters, both incoming and outgoing, were stapled together by subject. Arrangement was roughly chronological.
  - List of Topics In Stewart Collection
  - Arrangements of Fugitive Reunion, Correspondence. Covers period from, Oct. 21, 1955 to April 26, 1956. Undated.
  - Fugitive Reunion Arrangements - Miscellaneous. Consisting of calendar of events, newspaper clippings, list of guests, holograph notes of Merrill Moore’s suggestions, Vanderbilt Calendar.
  - Fugitive Finances - Consisting of vouchers, financial statements, and letters regarding the handling of finances for the Fugitive Reunion. Letters from, March, 1956-May, 1957. Undated.
  - Fugitive Conference: Results - Correspondence dealing with conference., 1955-1957.
  - Fugitive Conference: Results - Clippings., April 28, 1956-May 4, 1956.
  - Calendar and Guest List.
  - Publishing Fugitive Conference (and matters related to Fugitives, Pictures, and Books) Correspondence.
  - Fugitive Reunion Photographs - Taken by Merrill Moore.
  - Fugitive Conference - Clippings. Arranged chronologically., Undated.
  - Stewart Correspondence Relating to Non-Fugitive Matters., April, 1956-April, 1957.
  - Correspondence with Richmond C. Beatty., Feb., 1957.
  - Syndication of Beatty’s literary column in the Nashville Tennessean. Correspondence, 1956-1958.
  - Supplementary Description - page 2 Book reviews written by Beatty.
  - Allen Tate Proposal - Correspondence concerns proposal to Fugitive Memorial Professorship., July-Oct., 1959.
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence., March 2, 1932-Dec. 4, 1967.
  - Class Roll Books, Five for years 1947, 1955, 1956, 1958.
  - Articles About Stewart.
  - Pamphlets belonging to Stewart.
  - Photograph of Davidson effigy.
- ALPHABETICAL LIST OF INCOMING CORRESPONDENTS RANDALL STEWART COLLECTION
  - Partial names are listed at the end. Folder indicated by F.
    - Adams, Dick, May 1, 1956. F 33.
    - Amacher, Anne, May 13, 1956. F 35.
    - March 17, 1957. F 40.
    - Anderson, Charles R., May 4, 1956. F 34.
    - Baker, Carlos, May 8, 1956. F 34.
    - Beatty, Richmond C., Feb. 5, 1957. F 40.
    - Feb. 23, 1957. F 40.
    - Bethurum, Dorothy, March 12, 1956. F 26.
    - April 16, 1956. F 29.
    - May 13, 1956. F 35.
    - June 3, 1956. F 37.
    - Nov. 19, 1957. F 43.
    - May 21, 1959. F 46.
    - May 8, 1956. F 34.
    - May 1, 1956. F 33.
    - March 13, 1956 to Henry Luce. F 26.
    - March 28, 1956. F 27.
    - April 9, 1956 to Ransom. F 29.
    - Blanchard, Harold H., May 8, 1956. F 34.
    - Bradley, Sculley, May 22, 1956. F 36.
    - Branscomb, Harvie, May 28, 1956. F 36.
    - June 12, 1956. F 38.
    - June 13, 1956 to Willard Thorp. F 38
    - June 26, 1956 to John Marshall. F 38
    - July 10, 1956 to John Marshall. F 38
    - April 10, 1957. F 41.
    - n.d. F 48.
    - Breis, Harvey, April 30, 1956. F 32.
    - Brooks, Cleanth, Nov. 10, 1955. F 21.
    - Feb. 16, 1956. F 24.
    - April 18, 1956. F 30.
    - Brown, Francis, Sept. 13, 1957. F 41.
    - Caesar, Kathleen, Feb. 5, 1958. F 44.
    - Carmichael, Oliver C, May 31, 1956. F 36.
    - Cheney, Fannie, Feb. 21, 1956. F 25.
    - Cobb, William C., Jan. 5, 1956. F 22.
    - Jan. 12, 1956. F 23.
    - Jan. 12, 1956 to Robert McGaw. F 23.
    - Feb. 28, 1956. F 25.
    - March 14, 1956. F 26.
    - June 13, 1956. F 38.
    - Jan. 15, 1958. F 44.
    - Jan. 15, 1958. F 44.
    - Coffin, Charles M., May 7, 1956. F 34.
    - Cohen, Barbara, April 8, 1956 to Robert McGaw. F 29.
    - Copeland, Edith, Oct. 9, 1957. F 42.
    - Cowan, Louise, Nov. 21, 1957. F 43. n.d. F 48.
    - Cunningham, James V., May 11, 1956. F 35.
    - Daley, Elizabeth Gill, May 30, n.d. F 48.
    - Davidson, Donald, May 11, 1956 to Dr. A. F. Kuhlman. 2 copies. F 35.
    - June 3, 1956 to Geoffrey Moore. F 37.
    - Dickey, Hervey, May 2, 1956. F 33.
    - Drewry, John E., Nov. 26, 1957. F 43.
    - Eaton, Vincent L., March 23, 1956. F 27.
    - March 30, 1956 to Overton Williams. F 28.
    - Oct. 24, 1956. F 39.
    - Ellegood, Donald, March 18, 1958 to Donald Davidson. F 45.
    - April 25, 1958. F 45.
    - Elliott, William Y., Nov. 25, 1955. F 21.
    - Feb. 27, 1956. F 25.
    - March 27, 1956. F 27.
    - March 30, 1956. F 28.
    - April 20, 1956. F 30.
    - Dec. 3, 1957. F 43.
    - Emerson, O. B., April 30, 1956. F 32.
    - Faulkner, Claude W., May 4, 1956. F 34.
    - Faverty, Fred., May 7, 1956. F 34.
    - Foster, Elizabeth, May 1, 1956. F 33.
    - Gerber, John C., Jan. 2, 1962. F 47.
    - Graf, LeRoy P., May 3, 1956. F 33.
    - Halpert, Violet, May 9, 1956. F 35.
    - Harwell, Coleman, Sept. 9, 1957. F. 41.
    - Sept. 18, 1957. F 42.
    - Feb. 20, 1958. F 44.
    - Hirsch, Goldie, Oct. 30, 1955 to Merrill Moore. F 20.
    - Howell, Isabel, Feb. 28, 1956. F 25.
    - Hunter, Anna C., Oct. 7, 1957. F 42.
    - Hunting, Robert, May 2, 1956. F 33.
    - Jackson, William A., April 30, 1956. F 32.
    - Jacobs, Robert D., March 25, 1956. F 27.
    - Kazin, Alfred, May 9, 1959. F 46.
    - Koller, Kathrine, May 8, 1956. F 34.
    - Kuhlman, A. F., April 18, 1956 to Donald Davidson-2 copies. F 30.
    - Luce, Henry R., March 17, 1956 to President Branscomb. F 27.
    - Lynn, Justine, Feb. 3, 1956. F 24.
    - May 1, 1956. F 33.
    - May 11, 1956. F 35.
    - Lytle, Andrew, Nov. 4, 1955. F 21.
    - Feb. 20, 1956. F 25.
    - n.d. F 48.
    - MacLean, Kenneth, May 3, 1956. F 33.
    - Marshall, John, March 9, 1956. F 26.
    - April 18, 1956. F 30.
    - May 24, 1956 to Rubin. F 36.
    - June 8, 1956. F 38.
    - June 8, 1956. F 38.
    - July 3, 1956 to Branscomb. F 38.
    - July 9, 1956. F 38.
    - July 10, 1956. F 38.
    - Dec. 12, 1956. F 39.
    - April 4, 1957. F 41.
    - April 18, 1957. F 41.
    - McGaw, Robert M., Jan. 10, 1956 to William C. Cobb. F23.
    - March 8, 1056 to Jack DeWitt. F 26.
    - March 29, 1956 to Ransom, Tate, and Warren. F 28.
    - March 30, 1956 to Caedmon Sales Corp. F 28.
    - March 30, 1956 to Barbara Cohen and Marianne. F 28.
    - April 11, 1956 to Jack DeWitt. F 29.
    - April 25, 1956 to Barbara Cohen. F 31.
    - Moore, Geoffrey, Feb. 20, 1957. F 25.
    - May 23, 1956 to Donald Davidson. F 36.
    - Moore, Merrill, Oct. 27, 1955. F 20.
    - Oct. 29, 1955. F 20.
    - Dec. 5, 1955. F 20.
    - April 11, 1956 to Harvie Branscomb. F 29
    - April 17, 1956. F 30.
    - April 27, 1956. 2 letters. F 31.
    - April 30, 1956. F 32.
    - June 1, 1956. F 37.
    - June 4, 1956. F 37.
    - Jan. 21, 1957 to Mary O. Abbott. F 40.
    - Sept. 10, 1957 to Harvie Branscomb. F 41
    - n.d. F 48.
    - Moore, Mrs. Merrill, Nov. 25, 1957. F 43.
    - Jan. 22, 1958. F 44.
    - Morison, S. E., March 2, 1932. F 19.
    - Morrissey, Eleanor F., May 9, 1956. F 35.
    - Nesbitt, George, May 4, 1956. F 34.
    - Owsley, Frank L., March 15, 1956. F 26.
    - Owsley, Harriet C., Nov. 24, 1957. F 43.
    - Pearce, Roy, Aug. 29, 1956. F 38.
    - Pearson, Norman H., Jan. 29, 1953. F 19.
    - Feb. 17, 1956. F 24.
    - March 8, 1956. F 26.
    - Phillips, Bob, Jan. 28, 1958. F 44.
    - Pomfret, Jack, April 26, 1956. F 31.
    - Purdy, Rob Roy, June 21, 1957 to Rubin. F 41.
    - Ransom, John C., Oct. 29, 1955. F 20.
    - Feb. 7, 1956. F 24.
    - Feb. 18, 1956. F 24.
    - April 2, 1956. F 29.
    - May 1, 1956. F 33.
    - May 26, 1956. F 36.
    - March 27, 1957. F 40.
    - Oct. 18, 1957. F 42.
    - Nov. 19, 1957. F 43.
    - Feb. 25, 1959. F 46.
    - March 3, 1959. F 46.
    - Feb. 1, n.d. F 48.
    - Rhind, Flora M. (of Rockefeller F.), Oct. 18, 1955 to Robert Spiller. F 20.
    - Rock, Virginia, April 4, 1956. F 29.
    - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., March 22, 1955 to Huntingdon Cairns. F 19.
    - May 27, 1955 to John Marshall. F 19.
    - July 19, 1955 to John Marshall. F 19.
    - Oct. 10, 1955. F 20.
    - Dec. 1, 1955. F 22.
    - March 8, 1956. F 26.
    - March 22, 1956. F 27.
    - April 16, 1956. F 29.
    - April 17, 1956. F 29.
    - April 24, 1956. F 30.
    - May 29, 1956. F 36.
    - June 5, 1956. F 37.
    - Sept. 13, 1956. F 39.
    - Sept. 19, 1956. F 39.
    - Nov. 29, 1956. F 39.
    - Dec. 1, 1956. F 39.
    - Dec. 14, 1956. F 39.
    - Jan. 10, 1957. F. 40.
    - June, 6, 1957 to Rob R. Purdy. F 41.
    - Sept. 23, 1957. F 42.
    - Nov. 3, 1957. F 42.
    - Nov. 19, 1957. F 43.
    - Jan. 28, 1958. F 44.
    - Dec. 8, 1958. F 45.
    - Jan. 2, 1959. F 45.
    - Jan. 3, 1959. F 45.
    - Jan. 13, 1959. F 46.
    - Jan. 23, 1959. F 46.
    - n.d. F 48.
    - n.d. to John Marshall. F 48.
    - Monday. F 48.
    - Spiller, Robert E. Starr, Elizabeth Stevenson, Alec B.
    - Spiller, Robert E., March 9, 1956. F 26.
    - Starr, Elizabeth, n.d. F 48.
    - Stevenson, Alec B., March 28, 1956. F 27.
    - May 1, 1956. F 33.
    - May 9, 1956. F 35.
    - Dee. 23, 1957. F 43.
    - Stewart, John L., Jan. 21, 1956. F 23.
    - May 30, 1956. F 36.
    - Sept. 28, 1956. F 39.
    - Stowe, H. Lloyd, March 27, 1957. F 40.
    - Tate, Allen, Oct. 27, 1955. F 20.
    - Jan. 27, 1956. F 23.
    - Feb. 9, 1956. F 24.
    - Feb. 17, 1956. F 24.
    - April 11, 1956 to Harvie Branscomb. F 29.
    - April 18, 1956. F 30.
    - April 28, 1956. F 32.
    - May 10, 1956. F 35.
    - Oct. 25, 1957. F 42.
    - Jan. 14, 1958. F 44.
    - Jan. 15, 1958. F 44.
    - July 30, 1959. F 46.
    - Aug. 11, 1959. F 46.
    - Aug. 29, 1959 to Henry C. Alexander and Benjamin Tate, 2 copies. F 47.
    - Oct. 2, 1959. F 47.
    - Taylor, George Rogers, March 19, 1956. F 27.
    - Taylor, Walter F., May 8, 1956. F 34.
    - Thompson, E. B., Dec. 6, 1957. F 43.
    - Thorp, Willard, Oct. 28, 1955. F 20.
    - Feb. 23, 1956. F 25.
    - April 20, 1956. F 30.
    - June 5, 1956 to Harvie Branscomb. F 37
    - Nov. 18, 1957. F 42.
    - Vanderbilt, Harold S., April 26, 1956. F 31.
    - Wade, John Donald, April 10, 1956. F 29.
    - Ward, John W., April 28, 1956. F 32.
    - Warren, Robert P., Nov. 19, 1955. F 21.
    - Jan. 27, 1956. F 23.
    - March 28, 1956. F 27.
    - Nov. 8, 1957. F 42.
    - Jan. 4, 1959. F 45.
    - Jan. 14, 1959. F 46.
    - Waterfield, C. A., n.d. F 48.
    - Weaver, Mrs. Herbert, May 9, 1956. F 35.
    - Whicher, George, Oct. 25, 1951. F 19.
    - Wills, Jesse, Nov. 19, 1957. F 43.
    - Sept. 28, 1959. F 47.
    - Wriston, Marguerite, Sept. 25, 1958. F 45.
    - May 24, 1959. F 46.
    - Dave, May 1, 1956. F 33.
    - Dave and Candace, April 30, 1956. F 32.
    - Ed, April 27, 1956. F 31.
    - Ellene, June 6, 1956. F 37.
    - George, Dec. 4, 1967, to Mrs. Stewart. Possibly George Core. F 47.
- SUPPLEMENTARY LIST OF CORRESPONDENTS
  - The following pages list the Stewart correspondence as it was topically grouped in Dr. Stewart’s files. Unlike the original arrangement, however, they are listed alphabetically.
- FUGITIVE REUNION ARRANGEMENTS
  - Bethurum, Dorothy, March 12, 1956; April 16, 1956.
  - Branscomb, Harvie, March 13, 1956 to Henry Luce; March 28, 1956; April 9, 1956 to Ransom.
  - Brooks, Cleanth, Nov. 10, 1955; Feb. 16, 1956; April 18, 1956. Cheney, Fannie - Feb. 21, 1956.
  - Cobb, William C. of Rockefeller Foundation, Jan. 5, 1956; Jan. 12, 1956; Feb. 28, 1956; Jan. 12, 1956 to Robert McGaw; March 14, 1956.
  - Cowan, Louise, n.d.
  - Eaton, Vincent L., March 23, 1956; March 30, 1956 to Overton Williams; Elliott, William Y. - Nov. 25, 1955; Feb. 27, 1956; March 27, 1956; March 30, 1956; April 20, 1956.
  - Hirsch, Goldie, Oct. 30, 1955 to Merrill Moore.
  - Howell, Isabel, Feb. 28, 1956.
  - Jacobs, Robert D., March 25, 1956.
  - Luce, Henry R., March 17, 1956 to President Branscomb.
  - Lytle, Andrew, Nov. 4, 1955; Feb. 20, 1956; n-.d.
  - Marshall, John, March 9, 1956; April 18, 1956.
  - McGaw, Robert M., Jan. 10, 1956 to William C. Cobb; March 29, 1956 to Ransom, Tate, and Warren; March 30, 1956 to Caedmon Sales Corp.
  - Moore, Merrill, Oct. 27, 1955; Oct. 29, 1955; n.d.; Dec. 5, 1955; April 11, 1956 to Harvie Branscomb; April 17, 1956; April 27, 1956 - 2 letters.
  - Owsley, Frank L., March 15, 1956.
  - Peck, Genevieve, for Merrill Moore - Feb. 17, 1956; March 8, 1956.
  - Ransom, Jchn C., Oct. 29, 1955; Feb. 7, 1956; Feb. 18, 1956; April 2, 1956.
  - Rhind, Flora M. of Rockefeller Foundation, Oct. 18, 1955 to Robert Spiller.
  - Rubin, Louis D., March 22, 1955 to Huntingdon Cairns; Oct. 10, 1955; March 22, 1956; April 16, 1956; April 17, 1956; April 24, 1956.
  - Spiller, Robert E., March 9, 1956.
  - Stevenson, Alec B., May 1, 1956; March 28, 1956.
  - Stewart, John L., Jan. 21, 1956.
  - Stewart, Randall, Nov. 23, 1955 with enclosure of two letters dated Oct. 25, 1955 to Jesse Wills; Jan. 25, 1956 to John C. Ransom; Jan. 25, 1956 to Robert P. Warren; Jan. 25, 1956 to Allen Tate; Jan. 30, 1956 to John L. Stewart; Feb. 14, 1956 to Tate; Feb. 14, 1956 to Warren; Feb. 14, 1956 to Andrew Lytle; Feb. 14, 1956 to Cleanth Brooks; Feb. 14, 1956 to Ransom; Feb. 20, 1956 to Ransom; Feb. 26, 1956 to Isabel Howell; March 6, 1956 - form letter to Fugitives and Inter–locutor-Critics; March 7, 1956 to William C. Cobb; March 11, 1956 to Fugitives; March 22, 1956 to Bill Elliott; memorandum to Fugitives, March 26, 1956; March 29, 1956 to Vincent L. Eaton; April 17, 1956 to Alec B. Stevenson; April 20, 1956 to Tate; April 20, 1956 to Chancellor; April 20, 1956 to Ransom; April 20, 1956 to Cleanth Brooks; April 24, 1956 to Harold Vanderbilt; April 26, 1956 to Allen Tate.
  - Tate, Allen, Oct. 27, 1955; Jan. 27, 1956; Feb. 9, 1956; Feb. 17, 1956; April 11, 1956 to Harvie Branscomb. April 18, 1956; April 28, 1956.
  - Taylor, George Rogers, March 19, 1956.
  - Thorp, Willard, Oct. 28, 1955; Feb. 23, 1956; April 20, 1956.
  - Vanderbilt, Harold S., April 26, 1956.
  - Wade, John Donald, April 10, 1956.
  - Warren, Robert P., Nov. 19, 1955; Jan. 27, 1956; March 28, 1956.
- PUBLISHING FUGITIVE CONFERENCE
  - Amacher, Anne, March 17, 1957.
  - Bethurum, Dorothy, Nov. 19, 1957; May 21, 1959.
  - Cobb, William C., Jan. 15, 1958; Jan. 15, 1958. Cowan, Louise - Nov. 21, 1957.
  - Davidson, Donald, June 3, 1956 to Geoffrey Moore. Ellegood, Donald - April 25, 1958; March 18, 1958 to Donald Davidson.
  - Elliott, William Y., Dec. 3, 1957.
  - Kazin, Alfred, May 9, 1959.
  - Moore, Geoffrey, Feb. 20, 1957; May 23, 1956 to Donald Davidson.
  - Moore, Merrill, Jan. 21, 1957 to Mary 0. Abbott; Sept. 10, 1957 to Harvie Branscomb.
  - Moore, Mrs. Merrill, Nov. 25, 1957; Jan. 22, 1958.
  - Owsley, Harriet C., Nov. 24, 1957.
  - Pearce, Roy, Aug. 29, 1956.
  - Purdy, Rob Roy, June 21, 1957 to Rubin.
  - Ransom, John C., Oct. 18, 1957; Nov. 19, 1957; Feb. 1, n.d.
  - Rubin, Louis, May 29, 1956; June 5, 1956; Sept. 13, 1956; Sept. 19, 1956; n.d.; Nov. 29, 1956; Dec. 10, 1956; Dec. 14, 1956; Jan. 10, 1957; June 6, 1957 to Rob Roy Purdy; Sept. 23, 1957; Nov. 3, 1957; Nov. 19, 1957; Jan. 28, 1958; Dec. 8, 1958; Jan. 2, 1959. Jan. 3, 1959; Jan. 13, 1959; Jan. 23, 1959.
  - Starr, Elizabeth, n.d.
  - Stevenson, Alec B., Dec. 23, 1957.
  - Stewart, John L., Sept. 28, 1956; May 30, 1956.
  - Stewart, Randall, March 6, 1956 to Tate; Sept. 27, 1957; Oct. 24, 1957 to Warren; Oct. 24, 1957 to Tate; Nov. 13, 1957 to Participants in Fugitive Conf. - 3 copies, 2 with notes from participants. Nov. 15, 1957 to Mrs. Alfred Starr; Nov. 15, 1957 to Mrs. Merrill Moore; Nov. 15, 1957 to Mrs. Frank L. Owsley, Jr.; Dec. 3, 1957 to Mrs. Merrill Moore; Dec. 9, 1957; Dec. 19, 1957 to Harvie Branscomb; Jan. 10, 1958 to Ransom; Jan. 10, 1958 to Warren; Jan. 10, 1958 to Tate; Jan. 17, 1958 to Tate; Jan. 17, 1958 to William C. Cobb; April 29, 1958 to Donald Ellegood; June 12, 1959 to Marguerite Wristin; Dec. 10, 1958 to Louis Rubin; Dec. 30, 1958 to Tate; Dec. 30, 1958 to Ransom; Dec. 3, 1958 to Rubin; Jan. 6, 1959 to Rubin; Feb. 1, 1958 to Rubin; Dec. 16, 1957 to Rubin; Nov. 5, 1957 to Rubin; Sept. 20, 1957 to Rubin; Jan. 11, 1958 to Rubin; Dec. 11, 1956 to Rubin; June 2, 1956 to Rubin - 2 copies; Sept. 18, 1956; Nov. 30, 1956 to John L. Stewart; June 2, 1956 to John L. Stewart; June 6, 1956 to Rubin; Dec. 3, 1956 to Rubin.
  - Tate, Allen, Oct. 25, 1957; Jan. 15, 1958; Jan. 14, 1958.
  - Thorp, Willard, Nov. 18, 1957.
  - Warren, Robert P., Nov. 8, 1957; Jan. 14, 1958; Jan. 4, 1959.
  - Wills, Jesse, Nov. 19, 1957; Wriston, Marguerite - Sept. 25, 1958; May 24, 1959.
- FUGITIVE CONFERENCE: RESULTS
  - Adams, Dick, May 1, 1956.
  - Amacher, Anne Ward, May 13, 1956.
  - Anderson, Charles R., May 4, 1956.
  - Baker, Carlos, May 8, 1956.
  - Bethurum, Dorothy, May 13, 1956. June 3, 1956.
  - Blanchard, Harold H., May 8, 1956. Bradley, Sculley; May 1, 1956.
  - Branscomb, Harvie, May 8, 1956; June 13, 1956 to Willard Thorp.
  - Breis, Harvey, April 30, 1956.
  - Cobb, William C., June 13, 1956.
  - Coffin, Charles M., May 7, 1956.
  - Cohen, Barbara, April 8, 1956 to Robert McGaw.
  - Cunningham, James V., May 11, 1956.
  - Daley, Elizabeth Gill, May 30, n.d.
  - Dickey, Hervey, May 2, 1956.
  - Emerson, O. B., April 30, 1956.
  - Faulkner, Claude W., May 4, 1956.
  - Faverty, Fred, May 7, 1956.
  - Foster, Elizabeth, May 1, 1956.
  - Graf, LeRoy P., May 3, 1956.
  - Halpert, Violet, May 9, 1956.
  - Hunting, Robert, May 2, 1956.
  - Jackson, William A., April 30, 1956.
  - Koller, Kathrine, May 8, 1956.
  - Lynn, Justine, May 1, 1956; May 11, 1956.
  - MacLean, Kenneth, May 3, 1956.
  - Marshall, John, June 8, 1956; May 24, 1956 to Rubin.
  - McGaw, Robert, April 25, 1956 to Barbara Cohen; April 11, 1956 to Jack DeWitt; March 30, 1956, to Barbara Cohen and Marianne Roney; March 8, 1956 to Jack DeWitt.
  - Moore, Merrill, April 30, 1956; June 1, 1956; June 4, 1956. Morrissey, Eleanor F. - May 9, 1956.
  - Nesbitt, George, May 4, 1956. Pomfret, Jack - April 26, 1956.
  - Ransom, John C., May 1, ,1956; May 26, 1956; March 27, 1957.
  - Rock, Virginia, April 4, 1956.
  - Rubin, Louis, March 8, 1956; July 19, 1955 to John Marshall; May 27, 1955 to John Marshall; Dec. 1, 1955; "Monday"; n.d. to John Marshall.
  - Stevenson, Alec B., May 9, 1956.
  - Stewart, Randall, April 9, 1956 to Virginia Rock; May 22, 1956 to LeRoy P. Graf; May 7, 1956 to Harvie Branscomb; May 7, 1956 to Mr. and Mrs. Harold S. Vanderbilt; May 8, 1956 to Louis Rubin, original and carbon; May 9, 1956 to Ellen and Jesse Wills; May 9, 1956 to Fannie Cheney; May 9, 1956 to Isabel Howell; May 10, 1956 to Alec B. Stevenson; May 17, 1956 to Allen Tate; May 15, 1956 to Charles M. Coffin; May 16, 1956 to Mrs. R. E. Amacher; May 17, 1956 to Dorothy Bethurum; May 24, 1956 to Ralph Morrissey; June 1, 1956 to John Marshall; April 5, 1957 to Ransom.
  - Tate, Allen, May 10, 1956.
  - Taylor, Walter F., May 8, 1956.
  - Thorp, Willard, June 5, 1956 to Harvie Branscomb.
  - Ward, John W., April 28, 1956.
  - Waterfield, C. A., n.d.
  - Weaver, Mrs. Herbert, May 9, 1956.
  - Dave, May 1, 1956.
  - Dave and Candace, April 30, 1956.
  - Ed, April 27, 1956.
  - Ellene, June 6, 1956.
- FUGITIVE FINANCES
  - Eaton, Vincent, Oct. 24, 1956.
  - Marshall, John, Dec. 12, 1956.
  - Stewart, Randall, March 13, 1956 to Ransom; March 13, 1956 to Tate; March 14, 1956 to Davidson; March 14, 1956 to Warren; March 14, 1956 Merrill Moore; March 14, 1956 to Cleanth Brooks; March 14, 1956 to Andrew Lytle; March 14, 1956 to Bill Elliott; March 14, 1956 to Willard Thorp; March 14, 1956 to Frank Owsley; March 14, 1956 to Louise Cowan; March 14, 1956 to Robert D. Jacobs; April 20, 1956 to Overton Williams; Oct. 29, 1956 to Vincent Eaton; Dec. 17, 1956 to John Marshall; April 4, 1957 to H. Lloyd Stowe; April 5, 1957 to Overton Williams; March 22, 1957 to H. Lloyd Stowe; Dec. 17, 1956 to Overton Williams; May 22, 1957 to Leonard B. Beach.
  - Stowe, H. Lloyd, March 27, 1957.
- STEWART CORRESPONDENCE RELATING TO NON-FUGITIVE MATTERS
  - Branscomb, Harvie, April 10, 1997; June 12, 1956; June 26, 1956 to John Marshall; July 10, 1956 to John Marshall; May 28, 1956 to Robert P. Warren; May 22, 1956.
  - Carmichael, Oliver C., May 31, 1956.
  - Davidson, Donald, May 11, 1956 to Dr. A. F. Kuhlman - 2 cop. Kuhlman, A. F. - April 18, 1956 to Donald Davidson - 2 cop. Marshall, John - April 18, 1957; April 4, 1957; June 8, 1956; July 3, 1956 to Branscomb; July 9, 1956; July 10, 1956.
  - Stewart, Randall, June 4, 1956 to John Marshall; July 5, 1956 to John Marshall; May 20, 1956 to o. C. Carmichael.
- CORRESPONDENCE WITH RICHMOND C. BEATTY
  - Beatty, Richmond C., Feb. 5, 1957; Feb. 23, 1957.
  - Stewart, Randall, Feb. 15, 1957 to Beatty; Feb. 22, 1957 to Beatty; Feb. 26, 1957 to Beatty; Feb. 26, 1957 to Joseph J. Jackson.
- SYNDICATION OF BEATTY"S COLUMN (RICHMOND C.)
  - Brown, Francis, Sept. 13, 1957.
  - Caesar, Kathleen, Feb. 5, 1958.
  - Copeland, Edith, Oct. 9, 1957.
  - Drewry, John E., Nov. 26, 1957.
  - Harwell, Coleman, Sept. 9, 1957; Sept. 18, 1957; Feb. 20, 1958.
  - Hunter, Anna C., Oct. 7, 1957. Lynn, Justine - Feb. 3, 1956. Phillips, Bob - Jan. 28, 1958.